Register of the Commonwealth Club of California records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Program File, 1916-2006 (Boxes 382-605)
  - 1998
    - Lynch, Peter (Box-folder 593: 24)
    - McBride, Ann (Box-folder 593: 25)
    - McColl, Hugh (Box-folder 593: 26)
    - McCourt, Frank (Box-folder 593: 27)
    - McGwire, Mark (Box-folder 593: 28)
    - McKenna, Kevin (Box-folder 593: 29)
    - McKinnon, Ronald (Box-folder 593: 30)
    - McNealy, Scott (Box-folder 593: 31)
    - Maddox, John (Box-folder 593: 32)
    - Malott, John R. (Box-folder 593: 33)
    - Marin Shakespeare Company (Box-folder 593: 34)
    - Mayes, Frances (Box-folder 593: 35)
    - Metz, Michael (Box-folder 593: 36)
    - Meyer, Christopher (Box-folder 593: 37)
    - Michelman, Kate (Box-folder 593: 38)
    - Miller, Diane Disney (Box-folder 593: 39)
    - Mitchell, George (Box-folder 593: 40)
    - Moe, Richard (Box-folder 593: 41)
    - Mondavi, Robert (Box-folder 594: 1)
    - Montoya, James M. (Box-folder 594: 2)
    - Moore, Geoffrey A. (Box-folder 594: 3)
    - Morgan, James C. (Box-folder 594: 4)
    - Morgan, Rebecca (Box-folder 594: 5)
    - Munroe, Tapan (Box-folder 594: 6)
    - Murphy, Michael (Box-folder 594: 7)
    - Murray, Charles (Box-folder 594: 8)
    - Myss, Caroline (Box-folder 594: 9)
    - Nakamatsu, Jon (Box-folder 594: 10)
    - Nathanson, Neil, and Lawrence Altman (Box-folder 594: 11)
    - Noonan, Peggy (Box-folder 594: 12)
    - Nuclear weapons in South Asia panel (Box-folder 594: 13)
    - Oakland Museum - Gold Rush (Box-folder 594: 14)
    - Oakland panel (Box-folder 594: 15)
    - Okimoto, Daniel (Box-folder 594: 16)
    - Oliver, April, and Jack Smith (Box-folder 594: 17)
    - Ornstein, Robert (Box-folder 594: 18)
    - O'Rourke, P. J. (Box-folder 594: 19)
    - Oyens, Gerrit de Marez (Box-folder 594: 20)
    - Panel of U.S. ambassadors to Africa (Box-folder 594: 21)
    - Parker, Karen (Box-folder 594: 22)
    - Pascarella, Carl (Box-folder 594: 23)
    - Patten, Christopher (Box-folder 594: 24)
    - Perlmutter, Louis (Box-folder 594: 25)
    - Petrocelli, Elaine (Box-folder 594: 26)
    - Poetry reading at Villa Montalvo (Box-folder 594: 27)
    - Polese, Kim (Box-folder 594: 28)
    - Post-election program (Box-folder 594: 29)
    - Privacy program (Box-folder 594: 30)
    - Prusiner, Stanley (Box-folder 595: 1)
    - Rabinowitz, Alan (Box-folder 595: 2)
    - Rawls, James J. (Box-folder 595: 3)
    - Reimer, Douglas (Box-folder 595: 4)
    - Reiner, Rob (Box-folder 595: 5)
    - Repetitive stress injury panel (Box-folder 595: 6)
    - Richardson, Len (Box-folder 595: 7)
    - Ridge, Tom (Box-folder 595: 8)
    - Riggs, Frank (Box-folder 595: 9)
    - Riley, Dawn (Box-folder 595: 10)
    - Ritter, Scott (Box-folder 595: 11)
    - Roberts, Cokie (Box-folder 595: 12)
    - Romer, Roy (Box-folder 595: 13)
    - Ross, Dennis (Box-folder 595: 14)
    - Rosset, Peter (Box-folder 595: 15)
    - Russia panel (Box-folder 595: 16)
    - Rymer, Russ (Box-folder 595: 17)
    - Saito, Kunihiko (Box-folder 595: 18)
    - Sanders, William (Box-folder 595: 19)
    - San Jose mayoral debate (Box-folder 595: 20)
    - San Jose Opera (Box-folder 595: 21)
    - Satcher, David (Box-folder 595: 22)
    - Scheffer, David John (Box-folder 595: 23)
    - Schnieder, Bill (Box-folder 595: 24)
    - Schor, Juliet (Box-folder 595: 25)
    - Schroder, Gerhard (Box-folder 595: 26)
    - Schultz, Richard (Box-folder 595: 27)
    - Schwartz, Stephen (Box-folder 595: 28)
    - Seifert, Werner (Box-folder 595: 29)
    - Shapiro, Lucy (Box-folder 595: 30)
    - Shapiro, Robert (Box-folder 595: 31)
    - Sheehy, Gail (Box-folder 595: 32)
    - Shirley, Donna (Box-folder 595: 33)
    - Shostak, Seth (Box-folder 595: 34)
    - Smaltz, Donald (Box-folder 595: 35)
    - Smith, Perry (Box-folder 595: 36)
    - Smolan, Rick (Box-folder 595: 37)
    - Sosa, Lionel (Box-folder 596: 1)
    - Souvorov, Igor (Box-folder 596: 2)
    - Sowell, Thomas (Box-folder 596: 3)
    - Spence, Gerry (Box-folder 596: 4)
    - Stahl, Lesley (Box-folder 596: 5)
    - Starr, Kenneth (Box-folder 596: 6)
    - State of the world forum (Box-folder 596: 7)
    - Stein, Eduardo (Box-folder 596: 8)
    - Strip-mining the sea panel (Box-folder 596: 9)
    - Superintendent of Public Instruction (Box-folder 596: 10)
    - Swindle, Orson (Box-folder 596: 11)
    - Tanaka, Hitoshi (Box-folder 596: 12)
    - Tao, House (Box-folder 596: 13)
    - Transportation panel (Box-folder 596: 14)
    - Tu, Long Yong (Box-folder 596: 15)
    - Tyson, Laura D'Andrea (Box-folder 596: 16)
    - Underhill, Paco (Box-folder 596: 17)
    - Unz, Ron, and Eugene Garcia debate (Box-folder 596: 18)
    - VanDerveer, Tara (Box-folder 596: 19)
    - Vaught, Wilma (Box-folder 596: 20)
    - Vedder, Amy (Box-folder 596: 21)
    - Walsh, Lawrence (Box-folder 596: 22)
    - Weil, Andrew (Box-folder 596: 23)
    - Weld, William (Box-folder 596: 24)
    - Werbach, Adam (Box-folder 596: 25)
    - Whitacre, Edward (Box-folder 596: 26)
    - Whitman, Christine (Box-folder 596: 27)
    - Wiley, Charles (Box-folder 596: 28)
    - Williams, Cecil (Box-folder 597: 1)
    - Wilson, Pete (Box-folder 597: 2)
    - Wolfe, Tom (Box-folder 597: 3)
    - Wolfensohn, James (Box-folder 597: 4)
    - Woolsey, Lynn (Box-folder 597: 5)
    - Year 2000 Panel (Box-folder 597: 6)
    - Yew, Lee Kwan (Box-folder 597: 7)
    - Zarb, Frank (Box-folder 597: 8)
    - Zhavania, Zurab (Box-folder 597: 9)
  - 1999
    - Abdullah II, King of Jordan (Box-folder 597: 10)
    - Adelman, Kenneth (Box-folder 597: 11)
    - Ahern, Bertie (Box-folder 597: 12)
    - Airport expansion panel (Box-folder 597: 13)
    - Alibek, Ken (Box-folder 597: 14)
    - Allen, Paul (Box-folder 597: 15)
    - Allison, Herbert M. (Box-folder 597: 16)
    - Ammiano, Tom (Box-folder 597: 17)
    - Andreessen, Marc (Box-folder 597: 18)
    - Angelides, Phil (Box-folder 597: 19)
    - Armstrong, Michael (Box-folder 597: 20)
    - Aroner, Dion (Box-folder 597: 21)
    - Bach, David (Box-folder 597: 22)
    - Balog, James (Box-folder 597: 23)
    - Bauer, Gary (Box-folder 597: 24)
    - Belo, Carlos (Box-folder 597: 25)
    - Bennett, Robert (Box-folder 597: 26)
    - Bennett, William J. (Box-folder 597: 27)
    - Berkeley Repertory Theatre (Box-folder 597: 28)
    - Bernes-Lee, Tim (Box-folder 597: 29)
    - Bloomberg, Michael (Box-folder 597: 30)
    - Bobb, Robert (Box-folder 597: 31)
    - Bock, Audie (Box-folder 597: 32)
    - Boxer, Barbara (Box-folder 597: 33)
    - Breslau, Karen (Box-folder 598: 1)
    - Brown, Lester (Box-folder 598: 2)
    - Brown, Willie (Box-folder 598: 3)
    - Buchanan, Patrick J. (Box-folder 598: 4)
    - Buchwald, Art (Box-folder 598: 5)
    - Bumpers, Dale (Box-folder 598: 6)
    - Burton, John (Box-folder 598: 7)
    - Butler, Robert (Box-folder 598: 8)
    - Campbell, Tom (Box-folder 598: 9)
    - Cartwright, Julianne (Box-folder 598: 10)
    - Case, Steve (Box-folder 598: 11)
    - Cepeda, Orlando (Box-folder 598: 12)
    - China in transition (Box-folder 598: 13)
    - China technology panel (Box-folder 598: 14)
    - "Church and State: The Debate" (Box-folder 598: 15)
    - Cisneros, Sandra (Box-folder 598: 16)
    - Clarke, John (Box-folder 598: 17)
    - Clinton, Hillary Rodham (Box-folder 598: 18)
    - Cogan, John F. (Box-folder 598: 19)
    - Cohen, Ben (Box-folder 598: 20)
    - Collins, Ellen (Box-folder 598: 21)
    - Corman, Roger (Box-folder 598: 22)
    - Crossing the Bay (Box-folder 598: 23-24)
    - Cuomo, Andrew (Box-folder 598: 25)
    - Cuomo, Mario (Box-folder 598: 26)
    - Dickey, Nancy Wilson (Box-folder 598: 27)
    - District attorney run-off election debate (Box-folder 598: 28)
    - Doubilet, David (Box-folder 599: 1)
    - Drew, Elizabeth (Box-folder 599: 2)
    - Duffield, David (Box-folder 599: 3)
    - Dyson, Esther, and Katie Hafner (Box-folder 599: 4)
    - East Bay dialogue on health care (Box-folder 599: 5)
    - East Bay economic summit (Box-folder 599: 6)
    - East Bay health dialogue (Box-folder 599: 7)
    - Edwards, Bob (Box-folder 599: 8)
    - Ehrenreich, Barbara (Box-folder 599: 9)
    - Ellison, Larry (Box-folder 599: 10)
    - Engler, John (Box-folder 599: 11)
    - Erdman, Paul (Box-folder 599: 12)
    - Eshoo, Anna (Box-folder 599: 13)
    - "Ethics and Post-Cold War Humanitarian Intervention: Beyond Realism and Idealism" (Box-folder 599: 14)
    - Faludi, Susan (Box-folder 599: 15)
    - Farmanfarmaian, Roxane (Box-folder 599: 16)
    - Feldt, Gloria (Box-folder 599: 17)
    - Fiorina, Carly (Box-folder 599: 18)
    - Forbes economic forecast panel (Box-folder 599: 19)
    - Ford, William Clay (Box-folder 599: 20)
    - Forum on the courts (Box-folder 599: 21)
    - Friedman, Thomas (Box-folder 599: 22)
    - Frowick, Robert (Box-folder 599: 23)
    - Fukuyama, Francis (Box-folder 599: 24)
    - Fuller, Millard (Box-folder 599: 25)
    - Gardner, Tom and Dave (Box-folder 599: 26)
    - Giles, Molly (Box-folder 599: 27)
    - Glassner, Barry (Box-folder 599: 28)
    - Goh, Chok Tong (Box-folder 599: 29)
    - Goltz, Thomas (Box-folder 599: 30)
    - "Good Citizen" program (Box-folder 599: 31)
    - Graham, Katharine (Box-folder 599: 32)
    - Grass, Guenter (Box-folder 599: 33)
    - "Great Debate" (University of California Berkeley - Stanford debate) (Box-folder 599: 34)
    - Greenwald, Hank (Box-folder 599: 35)
    - Gruwell, Erin (Box-folder 600: 1)
    - Habiger, Eugene (Box-folder 600: 2)
    - Hatch, Orrin (Box-folder 600: 3)
    - Hirshberg, Gary (Box-folder 600: 4)
    - Holiday, J. S. (Box-folder 600: 5)
    - Hu, Jason (Box-folder 600: 6)
    - Investment strategies for individual investors (Box-folder 600: 7)
    - Ireland, Patricia (Box-folder 600: 8)
    - Ivey, William (Box-folder 600: 9)
    - Jackson, Jesse (Box-folder 600: 10)
    - Jordan, Frank (Box-folder 600: 11)
    - Jowitt, Kenneth (Box-folder 600: 12-13)
    - Kawasaki, Guy (Box-folder 600: 14)
    - Keegan, Lisa (Box-folder 600: 15)
    - Kemp, Jack (Box-folder 600: 16-17)
    - Kennedy, David (Box-folder 600: 18)
    - Khrushchev, Sergei (Box-folder 600: 19)
    - Kilcullen, John (Box-folder 600: 20)
    - Klaus, Václav (Box-folder 600: 21)
    - Koskinen, John (Box-folder 600: 22)
    - Kovacevich, Richard (Box-folder 600: 23)
    - Krakauer, Jon (Box-folder 600: 24)
    - Kuleto, Pat (Box-folder 600: 25)
    - Lamb, Brian (Box-folder 600: 26)
    - Lambert, Richard (Box-folder 600: 27)
    - Lance, Sean (Box-folder 600: 28)
    - Landmine panel (Box-folder 600: 20)
    - Lantos, Tom (Box-folder 600: 30)
    - Lapham, Lewis (Box-folder 600: 31)
    - Lee, Hong-koo (Box-folder 601: 1)
    - Leiva, Jorge (Box-folder 601: 2)
    - Leno, Mavis (Box-folder 601: 3)
    - Lewinsky, Monica (Box-folder 601: 4)
    - Lewis, John (Box-folder 601: 5)
    - Lipton, James (Box-folder 601: 6)
    - Lipton, Robert J. (Box-folder 601: 7)
    - McAleese, Mary (Box-folder 601: 8)
    - McCain, John (Box-folder 601: 9)
    - McColl, Hugh (Box-folder 601: 10)
    - McCourt, Frank (Box-folder 601: 11)
    - Machimura, Nobutaka (Box-folder 601: 12)
    - Marceau, Marcel, and Jan Wahe (Box-folder 601: 13)
    - Marchi, Sergio (Box-folder 601: 14)
    - Marshall, Colin, Lord (Box-folder 601: 15)
    - Mayer, Henry (Box-folder 601: 16)
    - Mayoral debate (Box-folder 601: 17)
    - Mendez, Antonio (Box-folder 601: 18)
    - Microsoft panel (Box-folder 601: 19)
    - Milken, Michael R. (Box-folder 601: 20)
    - Minor, Halsey (Box-folder 601: 21)
    - Mitchell, Andrei (Box-folder 601: 22)
    - Moctezuma Barragán, Esteban (Box-folder 601: 23)
    - Monkman, Betty (Box-folder 601: 24)
    - Moscoso, Elisa (Box-folder 601: 25)
    - Naisbitt, John and Nana (Box-folder 601: 26)
    - Nash, Steven (Box-folder 601: 27)
    - Nasseri, Cyrus (Box-folder 601: 28)
    - Newton, Lloyd (Box-folder 601: 29)
    - Oakland Museum of California (Box-folder 601: 30)
    - Ogata, Sadako (Box-folder 601: 31)
    - Panetta, Leon (Box-folder 601: 32)
    - Parry, Robert (Box-folder 601: 33)
    - Paul, Caroline (Box-folder 601: 34)
    - Perry, William (Box-folder 601: 35)
    - Pinker, Steven (Box-folder 601: 36)
    - Press in the Internet (Box-folder 601: 37)
    - Prueher, Joseph (Box-folder 602: 1)
    - Quayle, Dan (Box-folder 602: 2)
    - Reilly, Clinton (Box-folder 602: 3)
    - Reno, Janet (Box-folder 602: 4)
    - Riley, Richard (Box-folder 602: 5)
    - Robbins, Donna Quinn (Box-folder 602: 6)
    - Roberts, Cokie (Box-folder 602: 7)
    - Robertson, Pat (Box-folder 602: 8)
    - Robinson, John (Box-folder 602: 9)
    - Robinson, Leonard (Box-folder 602: 10)
    - Rogers, Gary (Box-folder 602: 11)
    - Rorty, Richard (Box-folder 602: 12)
    - Rosenberg, Pamela (Box-folder 602: 13)
    - Ross, David (Box-folder 602: 14)
    - Rossotti, Charles (Box-folder 602: 15)
    - Sanford, Bruce (Box-folder 602: 16)
    - Scheck, Barry (Box-folder 602: 17)
    - Schlesinger, Laura (Box-folder 602: 18)
    - Schultz, Howard (Box-folder 602: 19)
    - Schwab, Charles (Box-folder 602: 20)
    - Shapiro, Robert (Box-folder 602: 21)
    - Shelley, Kevin (Box-folder 602: 22)
    - Shlaes, Amity (Box-folder 602: 23)
    - Shlain, Leonard (Box-folder 602: 24)
    - Shriver, Maria (Box-folder 602: 25)
    - Shultz, George P. (Box-folder 602: 26)
    - Sisulu, Shelia (Box-folder 602: 27)
    - Slater, Rodney (Box-folder 602: 28)
    - Smith, Anna Deavere (Box-folder 602: 29)
    - Smith, Jed (Box-folder 602: 30)
    - Sobel, Dava (Box-folder 602: 31)
    - Solomon, Norman, and Lois Melkonian (Box-folder 602: 32)
    - "Sophisticated Ellington" (performance) (Box-folder 602: 33)
    - Springsteen, Bruce (Box-folder 602: 34)
    - Steinbeck Center (Box-folder 602: 35)
    - Stephanopoulos, George (Box-folder 602: 36)
    - Strouse, Jean (Box-folder 602: 37)
    - Sullivan, Kathleen (Box-folder 602: 38)
    - Summers, Lawrence (Box-folder 602: 39)
    - Suskind, Ron, and Cedric Jennings (Box-folder 603: 1)
    - Sustainable development summit (Box-folder 603: 2)
    - Swain, Judith (Box-folder 603: 3)
    - Tan, Amy (Box-folder 603: 4)
    - Tannen, Deborah (Box-folder 603: 5)
    - Thomas, Christopher (Box-folder 603: 6)
    - Thompson, Mike (Box-folder 603: 7)
    - Thompson, Norma (Box-folder 603: 8)
    - Tiger, Lionel (Box-folder 603: 9)
    - Tung, Chee-hwa (Box-folder 603: 10)
    - Tyler, Patrick (Box-folder 603: 11)
    - "Ukraine and the West in the New Millennium" (Box-folder 603: 12)
    - Updike, John (Box-folder 603: 13)
    - Valenti, Jack (Box-folder 603: 14)
    - Varmus, Harold (Box-folder 603: 15)
    - Villalonga, Juan (Box-folder 603: 16)
    - Villaraigosa, Antonio (Box-folder 603: 17)
    - Voigt, Karsten (Box-folder 603: 18)
    - Vonnegut, Kurt (Box-folder 603: 19)
    - Von Stade, Frederica (with Lofti Mansouri and Stephanie von Buchau) (Box-folder 603: 20)
    - Walsh, Bill (Box-folder 603: 21)
    - Water program (Box-folder 603: 22)
    - "Water Rights, Water Wrongs" (Box-folder 603: 23)
    - Water series (Box-folder 603: 24-25)
    - Water transit international panel (Box-folder 603: 26)
    - Webb, James (Box-folder 603: 27)
    - Whitman, Meg (Box-folder 603: 28)
    - Wilson, William Julius (Box-folder 603: 29)
    - "Women's Roles in Global Leadership" (Box-folder 603: 30)
    - Woodward, Bob (Box-folder 603: 31)
    - Wrubel, Robert (Box-folder 603: 32)
    - Yongqiu, Wang (Box-folder 603: 33)
    - Yosano, Kaoru (Box-folder 603: 34)
    - Zedillo Ponce de León, Ernesto (Box-folder 604: 1)
    - Zinn, Howard (Box-folder 604: 2)
  - 2000
    - Annan, Kofi (Box-folder 604: 3)
    - Assad, Bashar (Box-folder 604: 4)
    - Bradley, Bill (Box-folder 604: 5)
    - Brundtland, Harlem (Box-folder 604: 6)
    - Bush, Jeb (Box-folder 604: 7)
    - Carter, Rubin (Box-folder 604: 8)
    - Chopra, Deepak (Box-folder 604: 9)
    - Christensen, Terry, and Larry N. Gerston (Box-folder 604: 10)
    - Clinton, Bill (Box-folder 604: 11)
    - Dell, Michael (Box-folder 604: 12)
    - Dhanapala, Jayantha (Box-folder 604: 13)
    - Fanning, Shawn (Box-folder 604: 14)
    - Gore, Al (Box-folder 604: 15)
    - Gross, Terry (Box-folder 604: 16)
    - Grove, Andrew (Box-folder 604: 17)
    - Hatch, Orrin (Box-folder 604: 18)
    - Hume, John (Box-folder 604: 19)
    - Jackson, Jesse (Box-folder 604: 20)
    - Kavan, Jan (Box-folder 604: 21)
    - Kelley, David E. (Box-folder 604: 22)
    - Knight, Philip (Box-folder 604: 23)
    - Lander, Eric (Box-folder 604: 24)
    - Lehrer, Tom (Box-folder 604: 25)
    - Marineau, Philip (Box-folder 604: 26)
    - Marron, Donald (Box-folder 604: 27)
    - Martin, Steve (Box-folder 604: 28)
    - Moore, Michael (Box-folder 604: 29)
    - Musharraf, Pervez (Box-folder 604: 30)
    - Nazarbayev, Nursultan (Box-folder 604: 31)
    - Platt, Lew (Box-folder 604: 32)
    - Putin, Vladimir (Box-folder 604: 33)
    - Quinn, Sally (with Ben Bradlee and Eric Tarloff) (Box-folder 604: 34)
    - Smith, Richard (Box-folder 604: 35)
    - Spillett, Roxanne (Box-folder 604: 36)
    - Stiglitz, Joseph (Box-folder 604: 37)
    - Swire, Peter (Box-folder 604: 38)
    - Zemen, Milos (Box-folder 604: 39)
  - 2001
    - Boies, David (Box-folder 605: 1)
    - DiIulio, John (Box-folder 605: 2)
    - Powell, Colin L. (Box-folder 605: 3)
    - Scowcroft, Brent (Box-folder 605: 4)
    - Terrorism (community forum), 2001 September 17 (Box-folder 605: 5)
  - 2004
    - Huffington, Arianna (Box-folder 605: 6)
    - Osborne, David (Box-folder 605: 7)
  - 2006
    - Lindh, Frank R. (Box-folder 605: 8)
- Printed Matter, 1903-2004 (Boxes 605-672)
  Collected news clippings, and club issuances and publications, arranged by physical form: clippings, promotional flyers, press releases, monographs, and serials. See also printing samples in Printing Records.
  - Collected news clippings, 1915-2002 (Box-folder 605: 9-16)
  - Collected news clippings, 1915-2002 (Boxes 606-617)
  - Collected news clippings, 1915-2002 (Box-folder 618: 1-2)
  - Club flyers, undated (Box-folder 618: 3)
  - Club press releases, 1969-1994 (Box-folder 618: 4-17)
  - Club monographs
    - Occupational Restrictions: A Study of the Laws of Eighteen Selected States, Covering the Requirements for Entering Occupations Therein, 1929 (Box 619)
    - The Legislature of California: Its Membership, Procedure, and Work, 1943 (Box-folder 620: 1)
    - The Population of California, 1946 (Box-folder 620: 2)
    - California Social Welfare, 1956 (Box-folder 620: 3)
    - Powers of the President in Foreign Affairs, 1945-1965, 1966 (Box-folder 620: 4)
    - Each a Mighty Voice: A Century of Speeches from the Commonwealth Club of California, 2004 (Box-folder 620: 5)
  - Club serials
    - Meeting notices, 1911-1921 (Box-folder 620: 6-7)
      Includes January mysteries notices.
    - Meeting notices, 1911-1921 (Box 621)
    - The Commonwealth.
      Weekly serial published as the Transactions, Part One. See also Transactions of the Commonwealth Club.
      - Notices and volumes 1-2, 1920-1926 (Box 621)
      - Notices and volumes 1-3, 1925-1927 (Box 621)
      - Volumes 3-5, 1927-1929 (Box 621)
      - Volumes 5-11, 1929-1935 (Box 622)
      - Volumes 12-21, 1936-1945 (Box 623)
      - Volumes 22-29, 1946-1953 (Box 624)
      - Volumes 30-37, 1954-1961 (Box 625)
      - Volumes 38-42, 1962-1966 (Box 626)
      - Volumes 61-64, 1967-1970 (Box 626)
        See also volumes 65-66 in box 1174
      - Volume 71, 1977 (Box 627)
      - Volumes 73-75, 1979-1981 (Box 627)
      - Volumes 81-82, 1987-1988 (Box 627)
      - Volume 82, 1988 (Box 628)
      - Volume 85, 1991 (Box 628)
      - Volume 87, 1993 (Box 628)
      - Volumes 90-91, 1996-1997 (Box 628)
      - Volumes 92-94, 1998-2000 (Box 629)
    - The Lamplighter, 1985-1986 (Box 629)
      Internal publication of club staff.
    - Progress reports. Annual reports of the club
      - Unnumbered volumes, 1906-1909 (Box 630)
      - Volumes 4-19, 1910-1925 (Box 630)
      - Volumes 2-7, 1926-1931 (Box 630)
      - Volumes 8-20, 1932-1943 (Box 631)
      - Volumes 21-34, 1944-1957 (Box 632)
      - Volumes 35-68, 1958-1974 (Box 633)
    - Transactions of the Commonwealth Club of California, Parts One and Two, bound volumes unless otherwise noted
      - Volumes 1-5, 1903-1911 (Box 634)
      - Volumes 6-9, 1911-1915 (Box 635)
      - Volumes 10-13, 1915-1919 (Box 636)
      - Volumes 14-17, 1919-1923 (Box 637)
      - Volumes 18-20, 1923-1926 (Box 638)
      - Volumes 21-22, 1926-1927 (Box 639)
      - Volumes 23-24, 1928-1929 (Box 640)
      - Volumes 25-27, 1930-1932 (Box 641)
      - Volumes 28-31, 1933-1936 (Box 642)
      - Volumes 32-35, 1937-1940 (Box 643)
      - Volumes 36-39, 1941-1944 (Box 644)
      - Volumes 40-43, 1945-1949 (Box 645)
      - Volumes 44-47, 1949-1953 (Box 646)
      - Volumes 48-51, 1953-1957 (Box 647)
      - Volumes 52-55, 1957-1961 (Box 648)
      - Volumes 56-59, 1961-1965 (Box 649)
      - Volumes 60-63, 1966-1969 (Box 650)
      - Volumes 64, 1970 (Box 651)
      - Volumes 67-71, 1973-1977 (Box 651)
      - Volumes 72-75, 1978-1981 (Box 652)
      - Volumes 76-78, 1982-1984 (Box 653)
      - Volume 79, 1985 (Box 654)
        Unbound issues; may be incomplete.
      - Volumes 80-81, 1986-1987
      - Volumes 82-84, 1988-1990 (Box 655)
      - Volume 85, 1991 (Box 656)
      - Volumes 86-87, 1992-1993
      - Volume 88, 1994 (Box 657)
      - Volume 89, 1995
      - Volume 90, 1996
      - Volumes 92-93, 1998-1999 (Box 658)
      - 2000
      - Volume 94 (Box 659)
    - Reports of the study sections
      - 1904-1908 (Box 659)
      - 1909-1912 (Box 660)
      - 1913-1915 (Box 661)
      - 1916-1918 (Box 662)
      - 1919-1922 (Box 663)
      - 1923-1926 (Box 664)
      - 1927-1930 (Box 665)
      - 1931-1935 (Box 666)
      - 1936-1941 (Box 667)
      - 1942-1948 (Box 668)
      - 1949-1958 (Box 669)
      - 1959-1971 (Box 670)
      - 1972-1981 (Box 671)
    - Transactions of the Commonwealth Club of California (volumes 1-75, 77, 78, 93), 1903-1981, 1983-1984, 1999 (Box 672)
      Microfilm
- Subject File, 1915-2002 (Boxes 673-680)
  Reports, correspondence, minutes of meetings, instructions, histories, notes, maps, charts, schedules, flyers, conference materials, exhibit proposals, press summaries, and printed matter, arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Adams, Edward, 1927 (Box-folder 673: 1)
  - Africa, 1978 (Box-folder 673: 2)
  - American Red Cross
    - Pacific Division, 1918-1919 (Box-folder 673: 3-4)
    - Second Red Cross War Fund, 1918-1920 (Box-folder 673: 5)
  - Angola, 1983 (Box-folder 673: 6)
  - Armenian and Syrian Relief Campaign, 1919 (Box-folder 673: 7)
  - Art exhibits, 1989-1993 (Box-folder 673: 8-20)
  - Bay Area Council, 1950-1965 (Box-folder 674: 1-2)
  - Belli and Cutter Laboratories, 1961 (Box-folder 674: 3)
  - California Constitutional Commission (report), 1930 (Box-folder 674: 4-6)
  - City Commons Club of Berkeley, 1989 (Box-folder 674: 7)
  - Civilian Defense, 1954 (Box-folder 674: 8)
  - Conference on Prohibition amendments, 1917 (Box-folder 674: 9)
  - Conference on U.S.-Mexican relations, 1979 (Box-folder 674: 10)
  - Cosmic lady, undated (Box-folder 674: 11)
  - Cuba, 2002, 1943 February-July (Box-folder 674: 12)
  - Detroit riot (Box-folder 674: 13-15)
  - Detroit riot, 1943 February-July (Box-folder 675: 1-2)
  - Electric power development in the United States, 1916 (Box-folder 675: 3-7)
  - Gold quill awards, 1980 (Box-folder 675: 8)
  - Hearing aids, 1937 (Box-folder 676: 1)
  - Hill, Windham, 1989 (Box-folder 676: 2)
  - Indians of Northeastern California, 1921 (Box-folder 676: 3)
  - Los Angeles Town Hall, minutes of meetings, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 676: 4-5)
  - Left wing material, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 676: 6)
  - Lithograph, George, 1979 (Box-folder 676: 7)
  - Men of California, 1931-1948 (Box-folder 676: 8)
    Includes registration lists.
  - Military service, 1918 (Box-folder 676: 9)